[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of meal is the Native American dish called Alegria?", "correct_answer": "Candy", "incorrect_answers": ["Cake", "Drink", "Bread"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where does Sam work in the movie I Am Sam?", "correct_answer": "Starbucks", "incorrect_answers": ["Dennys", "IHOP", "7-11"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Vincent Price portrayed Egghead in what popular 1960s television series?", "correct_answer": "Batman", "incorrect_answers": ["Get Smart", "Superman", "Gilligans Island"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In order to adapt to the dry environment, cacti completely lost their leaves in the process of evolution.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the dinosaur that is a mortal enemy of the one-eyed weasel in the 2009 movie Ice Age 3?", "correct_answer": "Rudy", "incorrect_answers": ["Eddie", "Bobby", "Ruby"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The huge grain industry in Colorado gives rise to breweries. Which of the following owns the biggest single site brewery located in Golden, Colorado?", "correct_answer": "Molson Coors Brewing Company", "incorrect_answers": ["Anheuser-Busch", "Jacob Leinenkugel Brewing Company", "Highfalls Brewing Company"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What should a person do to escape the attack of a wombat in the wild?", "correct_answer": "Climb a tree", "incorrect_answers": ["Run", "Play dead", "Jump in a river"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What color did Tommy paint Oliver Wendell Holmes in Johnny Dangerously?", "correct_answer": "Purple", "incorrect_answers": ["Black", "Green", "Red"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What guitarist and singer fronted a band whose debut album was titled Are You Experienced?", "correct_answer": "Jimi Hendrix", "incorrect_answers": ["James Cagney", "James Brown", "Jim Morrison"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What action star played the lead role in the 1988 movie Bloodsport?", "correct_answer": "Jean-Claude Van Damme", "incorrect_answers": ["Arnold Schwarzenegger", "Sylvester Stallone", "Bruce Willis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the main ingredient of the traditional Indonesian meal called Rendang?", "correct_answer": "Meat", "incorrect_answers": ["Bananas", "Potatoes", "Rice"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Joe Pesci and Robert De Niro are the only actors from Raging Bull that Scorsese ever cast twice.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]